Next step is to put on concealer.
Now a lot of women don't realize this but when you put concealer on the eyelid and put a little bit of powder on top it keeps your eyeshadow on all day and it keeps it from creasing.
I know I have a lot of women that say they have there mascara on running or there eyeshadow creases or this would be keep it from doing that.
When you put the concealer and the powder it keeps the oils from coming through and it will keep your mascara and keep everything in place.
Most important you definitely need to put on a eye cream.
Putting on a concealer on a dry eye is only going to make your eye look really dry because the eye would suck up the moisture from the concealer and it would start to go into the lines.
So you just put your eye cream right at the corner edge and alway tap gently with your index finger.
No rubbing or tugging or pulling on the eye.
Then you want to use a concealer about a 1/2 shade lighter and I alway recommend just brushing it on.
I recommend brushes for pretty much everything and tapping it with a finger afterwards just to smooth it out.
then you want to put it up over the whole lid close this is just going to even out the whole skin tone and make a beautiful pallet to start with and then on the other eye.
Tap it in.
Always make sure that everything is blended so you can take a peak and we are ready to go on to the next step.